<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
     Copyright (C) 2021 The Android Open Source Project

     Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
     you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
     You may obtain a copy of the License at

          http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

     Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
     distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
     WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
     See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
     limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Affirmations</string>
    <string name="affirmation1">I am strong.</string>
    <string name="affirmation2">I believe in myself.</string>
    <string name="affirmation3">Each day is a new opportunity to grow and be a better version of myself.</string>
    <string name="affirmation4">Every challenge in my life is an opportunity to learn from.</string>
    <string name="affirmation5">I have so much to be grateful for.</string>
    <string name="affirmation6">Good things are always coming into my life.</string>
    <string name="affirmation7">New opportunities await me at every turn.</string>
    <string name="affirmation8">I have the courage to follow my heart.</string>
    <string name="affirmation9">Things will unfold at precisely the right time.</string>
    <string name="affirmation10">I will be present in all the moments that this day brings.</string>
    <string name="description1">He is no exception. Although he was born a Christian, according to some scholars, he did not speak the Old Testament. His father came to Rome in the fourth century. The second Patriarch ordered him to be taught at university; by the time he was 19 he had completed the law course to become a lawyer. His father died in the first half of the 20th century.</string>
    <string name="description2">I know that a lot of folks disagree with the use of words to describe a person. This isn\'t some random opinion, this is a fact.\n\nMany people make it quite clear that if my name is Taylor they don\'t follow me because no one likes to call me that. People are really going crazy when they hear a name and their friends say they hear me. People make false claims based on the fact that I\'m not cool like most others do. Even if most people don\'t agree or disagree with some of my words, it\'s very hard to have enough respect to see some of that being true when people are getting upset by some of my words and trying to get their emotions out of someone else\'s face.</string>
    <string name="description3">My first season was a very successful one thanks to my early success and my positive results in my sophomore year. As a result, I was able to continue as an active member of my family and community.\n\nHowever, my final year in college helped create a large community among the children of my family. For me, the community also supported my interests through volunteering. But, while I am happy to leave that community all alone and start a family, I also felt like I needed to provide additional guidance.</string>
    <string name="description4">Whether I\'m a first-generation student, an entrepreneur, an entrepreneur-to-be, or a person who is lucky enough to be in a job and succeed at a low wage, to learn humility and take a second step.\n\nBut a deep and beautiful soul is needed in this challenge. He or she is smart, insightful, and very different from everyone else. We all have a capacity for this. I can only hope our peers with whom we deal with these problems can make all these changes.\n\nBut there is still nothing simple about this. I have no idea how to make my own choices of what I can do with my brain, my emotions, or even that of my life. Even in this challenge, I didn\'t know, either. I\'m not a good athlete, and I\'m not a good teacher. I might get to ride a bicycle or go solo. When I\'m bored, I never leave work. Maybe I\'m more at ease than I might realize. I\'m better in this because this challenge is the perfect opportunity—the perfect opportunity to learn.</string>
    <string name="description5">I appreciate you having me back!\n\nI want to thank you for watching the last few episodes (though, now on to the last one). Please join us.\n\nWhat you\'ll hear\n\nIn this series with David\n\nI want to say with the exception of the first couple scenes with David that I am really glad I didn\'t have to worry about ending things at all. It just came up for a lot more listening. It felt good to read that your story, as well as the ending, wasn\'t going to hurt, especially in your first few episodes. And even to be able to enjoy the book feels like you\'re enjoying the book. I don\'t know, I wish someone would ask myself, do I really have to write this book? I can write, but I don\'t know. You have helped me realize that, right now. I\'m doing my best to be with you. I love you, and thank you so much for the time. You\'re fantastic and I hope you keep this wonderful book alive in the world of Star Trek.</string>
    <string name="description6">I didn\'t understand why they didn\'t ask me this question because they were so busy.\n\n"Don\'t tell him there\'s no good advice here."\n\nHe said, "But I\'ll do it until you get me a letter. That\'s all."\n\nI took it as a good thing.\n\nI couldn\'t explain why there\'s such no good advice in the end.\n\nAs I was doing my best for a while, the people who have made me feel so safe stopped talking. It was as natural as I thought.</string>
    <string name="description7">We\'re going to learn from each other\'s mistakes, but as always, we are together, we are our friends. We were together for four months. I\'ll never forget what he did for my friends. I won\'t forget the love he gave me. And I\'ll cherish those two forever.</string>
    <string name="description8">My family lives by the motto, "The way I see it, every person has a right to life." With this passion for the things of the moment, I hope that we can share that passion with our neighbors.\n\nThe following is a quick synopsis of this chapter. In this chapter, we will start by discussing the rights of the unborn and the rights of the unborn\'s parents, and then go through the process of getting married and raising a child. We may not need to go into too much detail about each of these topics, since we simply know that this chapter is going to do everything for you. First, the first thing to note before we begin: this is a comprehensive, open, and detailed chapter. We want you to read this chapter as thoroughly as possible, so you\'ll be able to do your part. Then, we will start by talking about some of the ways I find myself working through my marriage to get to this point and how he got involved in making decisions in this chapter. (We\'ll look at each of these aspects from the same perspective as we did in chapter 1.) Finally, there will be a number of things, not covered in the book, that we will discuss here, so let\'s get started.</string>
    <string name="description9">The "hitch" is to get to a point where we\'re satisfied with what we\'re doing and then take a hit to our self-esteem and it\'s not hard to see this as the beginning and the end of our struggle with narcissism. There is a clear end goal in each and every aspect of our life: happiness and fulfillment. To achieve it, we need to get it done fast and have some "real" goals in mind. It is hard to find a clear end that looks more achievable than what the individual needs. Narcissism is often characterized by a state of being self-pity or apathy, and is not at all uncommon to see the "bigger, brighter house" in question as a place of concentration and quiet.</string>
    <string name="description10">The last sentence of his speech was a declaration that his son, Naji, was not a slave (see p. 13).\n\nThe child was then given permission to remain in the village of Fajroi. The story goes that these villagers were told that the parents had become afraid when the two men were being tortured by the other children in the village. The village had been razed to the ground by their soldiers, who now had to be killed. The first son was born, after a successful escape from the prison where he was kept. And when Naji died, seven months before his father\'s execution, the villagers finally began to make sense of the death which had happened in the village, and the way that the two men had escaped.</string>
    <string name="change_theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">Expand Button</string>
    <string name="description_title">Description:</string>
    <string name="detail_fragment">See more</string>
</resources>